Noah Solano

33s Boulder Cir , Boulder, Colorado, United States, 80303 | 720-339-7487

ndsolano294@gmail.com

Experienced and motivated professional with over 5 years of dedicated service industry experience. Recognized for being a fast learner, meticulously organized, and possessing strong leadership qualities. My overarching career goal is to seamlessly integrate my diverse skill set and expertise acquired outside of computer science into the field, enhancing my computer science degree with practical application and innovation.

Professional Experience

Compass Group

September 2022 - Present

Shift Lead

Shift supervisor for a hybrid cafe/Capital One bank working on the food and beverage side. Additional responsibilities regarding catering, cash handling, inventory, and some administrative tasks.

Ziggi's Coffee

August 2019 - October 2022

Barista

Experience with registers, stocking, customer service, and preparing/serving drinks in a high-paced environment. Both cafe and drive-through experience. Gained experience with both closing and opening the store as well.

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Computer Science August 2020 - Present University of Colorado Boulder at Boulder CO

Highschool Diploma August 2016 - May 2020 Silver Creek High School at Longmont CO

Projects

MiniGit

A simplified version control system of Git where users can initialize repositories, add, remove, commit, and checkout files.

Pong Clone

A pong clone built from scratch in Python that had themes of one of my favourite classes, Pathway to Space. Fully functional and made extensive use of the turtle library for graphics and animation.

ThoughtSpot

An online journal where one may log daily activities whether it be for themselves exclusively, open to the public, or restricted to a select few peers. It will include different formats and functions depending on the user's intentions and goals. It can provide mental relief/stimulus and help you develop your mindfulness/introspection through a system that is typical of a physical form. All entries will be saved to a database so that users can easily access their profiles and postings from nearly any device.

Relevant Coursework

Discrete Structures

Algorithms

Linear Algebra with CS Apps

Principles of Programming Languages

Software Dev Methods and Tools

Operating Systems

Database Systems

Key Skills

C/C++

Python

Javascript

Scala

HTML/CSS

SQL

Git

Jira

Operating Systems

Software Development

Cyber Security

Critical Thinking

Organization

Time Management

Communication

Creativity